

Summary

Experienced Graphic Designer and Front-end Web Developer with more than 10 years of software experience and 5 years in production settings. Highly innovative utilizing automation and standardization to produce graphics. Managed production of large quantity orders of over 100,000 items for HGTV, Philadelphia 76ers, and Comcast.

Professional Experience

2019 – 21 Lead Graphic Designer, Denial Print Company, Folsom PA

- Automated tasks to increase the quality and consistency of production.
- Constructed a website and created a variety of online forms that increased the accuracy and volume of quotes created by the secretary.
- Produced a new file hierarchy that increased the efficiency and organization of an internal server.

Tasks: Prepress, Finishing, Quality Control, File Management, Product Finishing, Large Format Printing.

2018 Intern, Applied Image LLC, Freehold NJ

- Manufactured environmental large format graphics.
- Restored studio quality on a day to day basis.

Tasks: Pre-press, Finishing, Printing, Plotting, Weeding, Laminating, Studio Maintenance.

2016 – 18 Printer Technician, MICA, Baltimore MD

- Directed large format printers, film printers, and risograph printer to generate customer projects in a timely manner
- Educated the student body on file preparation and processes for output.
- Provided consultation to visiting artists on methods and preparations for work to be produced at our studio.

Tasks: Pre-press, Education, Consultation, Printing, Finishing.

2014 – 18 Studio Assistant, Various Artists, Baltimore MD

- Constructed custom hardware for home film studio.
- Debuted the artist first public installation in decades at the first annual *Light City Baltimore*
- Manufactured and installed a public installation to city code.

Education

2018	BFA Printmaking Maryland Institute College of Art (MICA), Baltimore MD	
Skills	Languages & Software	Skills
	Adobe Suite (Illustrator, Photoshop, After	Project Management, Customer Service,
	Effects, Indesign, Premiere, Audition, Medium)	A/V Production, Screen Printing, Large
	Spark AR, Rhinoceros, HTML, CSS, Javascript	Format Printing